What's on your mind?
Huh?
I thought we were going to
be honest with each other.
What if I end up hurting you...
That's... what I'm thinking about.
Why are you already worrying about that?
Because we're completely
different people...
Is anyone in the world exactly the same?
Dating is just two different people meeting
and figuring it out as they go.
Don't overthink it.
If you like someone,
you just like them.
What's this?
Why are your hands this cold?
Stop messing around.
Why?
Getting butterflies?
Hey.
Want to go stargazing with me?
"My Secret Vampire"
(Episode 7)
Where will you go after you move out?
Probably the dorms at first...
Then I'll think about
traveling during the break.
Where would you go?
Just... wander around a bit.
Backpacking abroad
has been my dream since I started college.
Oh, right.
Want to come with me?
I can't leave the country.
Why?
You're not some kind of fugitive, are you?
Don't be ridiculous.
Oh?
What's wrong?
The bracelet...
The bracelet is gone.
The bracelet?
Oh, that's the one I bought for you...
Found it!
Dongha!
Are you okay?
It looks rusty...
Juwon...?
It hurts!
You can stop now...
What's wrong with you...
Calm down...
It's me...
It's me!
Lee Juwon.
What if I end up hurting you?
That's... what I'm thinking about.
Because we're completely different...
Lee Juwon!
Dongha!
Juwon!
Han Dongha!
Hey.
Did you really hear that?
I'm sure the sound came from here...
The smell of blood...
Don't go.
Do you... not understand what's happening?
It's dangerous for you to be with me.
I'll decide if it's dangerous or not.
You almost died because of me.
- But I didn't die, did I?
- Hey! Han Dongha.
Didn't you say you liked me?
So...
The least you can do is explain
what on earth is going on.
You saw me drinking blood.
What more is there to explain?
This is why
I didn't want you to move in at first.
- You understand?
- You're the one who's afraid of getting hurt.
This isn't about me finding out.
You're just scared of
being abandoned again.
You're terrified because
you don't want to get hurt.
But...
I still like you.
So what am I supposed to do?
But I don't.
That's enough.
I told you to stop!
What are you, a fitness
freak? It's so loud...
Was the house always this quiet?
Tell me about it.
It wasn't like this when Dongha was here.
What's Juwon doing?
I don't know.
He won't come out of his room.
What about Seonjae?
He hasn't been back in days.
Dongha...
What do you think he's doing now?
He must be so mad at us, right?
Dongha!
Are you okay?
Are you guys vampires too... or something?
Let go of me.
Dongha.
Then,
the reason you let me move in,
was it because you needed my blood, too?
I thought you were my family...
I guess I was wrong.
Ugh, I shouldn't have gotten my hopes up.
I didn't want to drink Dongha's blood.
Really?
Didn't you say
that it could be addictive?
You believed that?
Of course.
What if you really started
going after Han Dongha?
I can't believe I'm
stuck with a guy like you.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
I'm craving the toast
Dongha used to make...
Why was that so much tastier?
It's all human food.
Lee Juwon.
Don't go.
You almost died because of me.
No.
It wasn't your fault.
Do you... not understand what's happening?
You almost died because of me.
- But I didn't die, did I?
- Hey! Han Dongha.
Didn't you say you liked me?
The least you can do is explain
what on earth is going on...
Oh?
Why'd you call me here? I'm busy!
No reason.
It's been a while. I missed you, Sis.
Are you feeling sick or something...?
Hold on.
This is a sample.
Try it.
Oh.
If we have this in the future,
we won't have to drink human blood?
Well...
There's no perfect substitute...
We'll just have to keep developing it.
Lee Juwon will probably be the happiest.
Hey, you're bringing up Juwon again?
Oh, right...
By the way.
Did you bring the thing I asked for?
Here.
But what's this for?
I figured someone could really use it.
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
But why would you go this far?
Because someone...
said I seemed like a good person.
But,
you really are a good person.
Me?
Yeah.
I can tell a good person when I see one.
Because it's the first
time I've ever heard that,
I wanted to try being that kind of person.
Why can't I see a single star...
What are you looking at?
Where'd you disappear to?
Oh, were you worried about me?
If I'd known, I would've
stayed away a few more days.
Just went around feeling sorry for myself.
A broken heart hurts, you know.
Are you talking about me?
Who else would I be talking about?
I'm sorry.
You regret it, don't you?
Regret letting Dongha go.
No.
I think this was the right thing to do.
Even though I think it was right...
But,
I lied until the very end.
Dongha was always honest with me.
But I couldn't do the same.
I'm such a coward...
Serves you right.
Among the games humans play,
there's one called 'Truth'.
And?
Well...
The game is just an excuse.
It's really just an excuse
to say what's truly on your mind.
Who's first?
Play by yourself.
Then I'll go first.
I'm giving up on you now.
I've thought about it...
It's your loss.
Your turn.
I...
I miss him.
Then just go see him.
(Sharehouse Rental Agreement)
(Address)
What would you do without me?
Thanks.
Geez.
"My Secret Vampire"